Guide to the Church Coalition for Human Rights in the Philippines records, 1982-1993.
Church Coalition for Human Rights in the Philippines records
- Correspondence relating to organizing the International Ecumenical Conference on the Philippines, 1983 (Box 35, Folder 10)
- International Conference on the Philippines, 1983-09-27-1983-10-02 (Box 35, Folder 11)
  Includes working papers
- Correspondence relating to organizing the International Conference on the Philippines, September 27-October 2, 1983, 1983-09-27-1983-10-02 (Box 35, Folder 12)
- Papers of the International Conference on the Philippines, September 27-October 2, 1983, 1983-09-27-1983-10-02 (Box 35, Folder 13)
- International Conference on the Philippines, 1983-09-27-1983-10-02 (Box 35, Folder 14)
  Includes handwritten notes, reports
- International Ecumenical Conference on the Philippines, 1983-11-17 (Box 35, Folder 15)
  US Host Committee final meeting
- International Ecumenical Conference on the Philippines (last two meetings), 1983 (Box 35, Folder 16)
- INFOS - Mindanao (International Forum for Solidarity - Mindanao), 1985-09-07-1985-09-21 (Box 35, Folder 17)
  Contains papers on the International Solidarity Conference on the Philippines
- International Forum on Solidarity - Mindanao - International Solidarity Conference on the Philippines Panel Breakfast, 1986 (Box 35, Folder 18)
- Keynote address to the International Solidarity Conference on the Philippines, September 7-21, 1985, 1985-09-07-1985-09-21 (Box 35, Folder 19)
- Papers of the International Solidarity Conference on the Philippines, September 7-21, 1985. Sponsored by INFOS - Mindanao, 1985-09-07-1985-09-21 (Box 35, Folder 20)
- Publications regarding Philippines, 1984-1988 (Box 35, Folder 21)
- Publications regarding Philippines, 1979-1990 (Box 35, Folder 22)
- Testimonies on human rights violations (in the Philippines): excerpts, 1984-1989 (Box 35, Folder 23)
- CONTAK - Philippines, 1992 (Box 36, Folder 1)
- Correspondence with Dave Schrock-Shenk re 100,000 Faces Project, 1993 (Box 36, Folder 2)
- Philippines bases network, 1992 (Box 36, Folder 3)
- Philippine Development Forum Steering Committee meeting, February 1, 1993, 1993-02-01 (Box 36, Folder 4)
- Interlink Reports re Philippine sugar industry collapse, 1985 (Box 36, Folder 5)
- Letter from GABRIELA, 1985 (Box 36, Folder 6)
- CONTAK - Philippines re Pentecost Peace Campaign Paper, 1986 (Box 36, Folder 7)
- NCCC-USA re letter of concern from US missioners in the Philippines, 1986 (Box 36, Folder 8)
- Ed de la Torre luncheon, 1986 (Box 36, Folder 9)
- Philippine Tribal Minorities, 1986 (Box 36, Folder 10)
- Luncheon for Karl Gaspar, February 28, 1986, 1986-02-28 (Box 36, Folder 11)
- re Film about Third World Seamen (mostly Filipinos) B. Clement, 1986 (Box 36, Folder 12)
- Letter from Enrique de la Cruz, Coordinator, Alliance for Philippine Concerns, 1986 (Box 36, Folder 13)
- The New Yorker article on Father Niall O'brien, 1986 (Box 36, Folder 14)
- Memo re Bishop Tiples Visit/Luncheon, April 3, 1986, 1986-04-03 (Box 36, Folder 15)
- National Ecumenical Conference on the Philippines, 1986-10-17-1986-10-18 (Box 36, Folder 16)
  "People's Power Hope in our Struggle for Justice," Philadelphia
- Ecumenical Movement for Justice and Peace (EMJP) Fact-finding Mission Report: Cagayan Valley, Kalinga-Apayao, November 4-9, 1985, 1985-11-04-1985-11-09 (Box 36, Folder 17)
- Conference proceedings, 1985-03-02-1985-03-03 (Box 36, Folder 18)
  GABRIELA General Assembly Binding Women for Reforms, Integrity, Equality, Leadership, and Action, Quezon City
- Task Force Detainees of the Philippines (TFDP): (brochure), 1984 (Box 36, Folder 19)
- Nobel Peace Prize for the Task Force Detainees of the Philippines, 1985 (Box 36, Folder 20)
- Christian for National Liberation: a CNL National Consultation Statement, 1985 (Box 36, Folder 21)
- Philippine Report issues, 1985-1986 (Box 36, Folder 22)
- Philippine lobbying, 1986 (Box 36, Folder 23)
- Committee for Justice for Domingo and Viernes: National newsletter, Spring 1986, 1986 (Box 36, Folder 24)
- International Day of Protest re 13th Anniversary of Martial Law, 1985 (Box 36, Folder 25)
- Rebecca Asedillo's "Cry of the People, the Philippines," in Network, November-December 1985, 1985-11-1985-12 (Box 36, Folder 26)
- Draft pastoral letter from US missionersin the Philippines to Christian Churches in the US October 1985, 1985-10 (Box 36, Folder 27)
- "Reaping the Whirlwind": film strip re Filipino women in Japan, 1985 (Box 36, Folder 28)
- Report on the Philippines by Jay Lintner, March 1985, 1985-03 (Box 36, Folder 29)
- PAG-ASA Newsletter, December 1985, 1985-12 (Box 36, Folder 30)
- Center for Nationalist Trade Unions - Mindanao, 1985 (Box 36, Folder 31)
- Far Eastern Economic Review, November 21, 1985 re "Philippines, the Red Tide", 1985-11-21 (Box 36, Folder 32)
- Church Network on the Philippines, 1985 (Box 36, Folder 33)
- Philippine Center for Immigrant Rights, 1985 (Box 36, Folder 34)
- Church resolutions on the Philippines - (USA), 1985-1986 (Box 36, Folder 35)
- Ecumenical Mission Study Theme Process, 1986 (Box 36, Folder 36)
- The Filipino Child's Link, June 1985, 1985 (Box 36, Folder 37)
- Simbayan, 1st Quarter, March 1985. Pub by Ecumenical Center for Development, 1985 (Box 36, Folder 38)
- Ecumenical Press Service, 85.12.11 "US Church Opposition to Filipino Government Grows", 1985-12-11 (Box 36, Folder 39)
- Correspondence and statements re Philippine elections, 1986 (Box 36, Folder 40)
- GABRIELA 1986 March Rally, 1986 (Box 36, Folder 41)
- GABRIELA Attendance of members at Nairobi Forum 1985, 1985 (Box 36, Folder 42)
- GABRIELA - includes correspondence, conference proceedings and reports, 1985 (Box 36, Folder 43)
- GABRIELA - includes correspondence, publications, 1985 (Box 36, Folder 44)
- Friends of Filipino People, 1979-1985 (Box 36, Folder 45)
- Health Action Information Network Philippines, 1985 (Box 36, Folder 46)
- Hsu, Victor/WCC Staff Visit to the Philippines, 1985 (Box 36, Folder 47)
- Addresses - Philippines, 1986 (Box 36, Folder 48)
- Amnesty International - Reports, 1985 (Box 36, Folder 49)
- Assassination of Benigno Aquino - Cables, etc., 1983 (Box 36, Folder 50)
- Base Christian Community - the BCC-Co Program: an orientation, 1983 (Box 36, Folder 51)
- Bello, Walden - includes articles and publications, 1985 (Box 36, Folder 52)
- Philippine Political Prisoners Resource Center, 1986 (Box 36, Folder 53)
- CAMIP: Campaign Against Military Intervention in the Philippines, 1984 (Box 36, Folder 54)
- Canada Asia Currents, Fall-Winter 1983, 1983 (Box 36, Folder 55)
- Canadian films, 1985 (Box 36, Folder 56)
- Contains newsclippings, 1985 (Box 36, Folder 57)
- Grassroots International, 1985 (Box 36, Folder 58)
- Filipino migrant workers, 1983-1985 (Box 36, Folder 59)
- Conference summary: Forum of Foreign Church Persons in Mindanao, Cebu City, February 25-28, 1985, 1985-02-25-1985-02-28 (Box 36, Folder 60)
- In the matter of the Political Asylum Application of Edwin C. Francisco, 1985 (Box 36, Folder 61)
- Philippines health campaign, 1985 (Box 36, Folder 62)
- "Filipino domestics in Hongkong" (newsclipping), 1985 (Box 36, Folder 63)
- Ecumenical Partnership for International Concerns - Philippines - includes correspondence, 1984 (Box 36, Folder 64)
- Karl Gaspar, 1984 (Box 36, Folder 65)
- Report of the International Commission of Jurists on Human Rights in the Philippines, 1984 (Box 36, Folder 66)
- Contains a correspondence from Robert F., Drinan, S.J. and a letter of thanks of Dr. A. Parong to Dr. Fine, 1984 (Box 36, Folder 67)
  Includes an article "US physician delegation urges probe of health worker persecution in Philippines," with picture of Dr. Jonathan Fine, American Medical Association
- Report of the International Ecumenical Conference of the Philippines (on) Cry of the People, Challenges to the Churches, New York, September 27-October 2, 1983, 1983-09-27-1983-10-02 (Box 36, Folder 68)
- Farmers Assistance Board, Inc. - includes correspondence, reports and minutes of meetings, 1979 (Box 36, Folder 69)
- FILINS (Filipino Information Service), 1979-1980 (Box 36, Folder 70)
- Jim Kurtz of Mennonite Central Committee, Volunteer in the Philippines, 1985 (Box 36, Folder 71)
- Fr. Tom Marti, 1986 (Box 36, Folder 72)
- Letter from the Methodists Federation for Social Action, 1985 (Box 36, Folder 73)
- MIPC Communications, April and September 1985 Issues. Pub by Mindanao Interfaith People's Conference Secretariat, 1985-04-1985-09 (Box 36, Folder 74)
- Key persons list, 1985 (Box 36, Folder 75)
- Ang Kapatid: newsletter of the KAPATID, 1984 (Box 36, Folder 76)
- Forum and Reception with Bobby Ortaliz, KMU, October 16, 1985, 1985-10-16 (Box 36, Folder 77)
- Pacific School of Religion Student-Faculty Exposure Tour to the Philippines, 1986 (Box 36, Folder 78)
- Philippine Center for Immigrant Rights, 1985 (Box 36, Folder 79)
- National Council of Churches in the Philippines, 1985 (Box 36, Folder 80)
- Philippine health and medical campaign, 1984-1985 (Box 36, Folder 81)
- Promotion of Church People's Rights: (brochure), Undated (Box 36, Folder 82)
- CCHRP statement of concern on the US role in the Philippines, 1985 (Box 36, Folder 83)
- Resource Center for Philippine Concerns, 1984-1985 (Box 36, Folder 84)
- Rev. Hans-Jochen Vogel, Chairman, Evangelical Student Chaplain's Conference in the GDR - correspondence, 1985-1986 (Box 36, Folder 85)
- Task Force Detainees of the Philippines, 1985-1986 (Box 36, Folder 86)
  Contains publications
- Task Force Detainees of the Philippines (nomination for the 1986 Nobel Peace Prize), 1986 (Box 36, Folder 87)
- Letter of Amando J. Malay, Sr. re TFDP's nomination for the 1986 Nobel Peace Prize, 1986 (Box 36, Folder 88)
- Project Proposal: University Christian Movement in New England Exposure Tour to the Philippine to be led by Kathryn Johnson, 1986 (Box 36, Folder 89)
- United Methodist General Conference Resolutions, May 1984, 1984-05 (Box 36, Folder 90)
- Makiisa-ka (Makabayang Kilusan Para Isulong ang Katarungan), November 13, 1981, 1981-11-13 (Box 36, Folder 91)
- CCHRP Steering Committee, 1985-01-1985-03 (Box 37, Folder 1)
  Includes minutes of meetings, correspondence, personal notes, publications, January-March 1985
- CCHRP Steering Committee meetings, 1991 (Box 37, Folder 2)
  Includes minutes and handwritten notes
- CCHRP, 1991 (Box 37, Folder 3)
  Includes correspondence and notes on presentations, group discussions and conversation with Tom O'Brien
- Papers on the 6th National Ecumenical Conference on the Philippines, 1990-11-16-1990-11-18 (Box 37, Folder 4)
  "Beating Swords into Plowshares: Toward a Sustainable Peace," Pasadena, CA
- CCHRP Steering Committee meetings - includes minutes and publications, 1990 (Box 37, Folder 5)
- CCHRP Personnel Committee - includes correspondence, memoranda, 1991 (Box 37, Folder 6)
- CCHRP finance - includes balance sheets and financial statements, 1990-1991 (Box 37, Folder 7)
- Philippine readings - includes news articles and publications on human rights, military bases, etc, 1992 (Box 37, Folder 8)
- PJAG draft resources for drafting NCCC document on US/Phil relations, 1992-1993 (Box 37, Folder 9)
- Philippines readings, 1993-1994 (Box 37, Folder 10)
  Includes newsletters, publications; draft program of the Christians for National Liberation; NDF's statements
- Philippine resources, 1989 (Box 37, Folder 11)
  Contains publications and newsclippings
- Philippine resources, 1985-1986 (Box 37, Folder 12)
- Philippine resources, 1985 (Box 37, Folder 13)
- Philippine workshop resources - Ecumenical study (USA), 1989 (Box 37, Folder 14)
- Ecumenical Mission on the Philippines, 1989 (Box 37, Folder 15)
  Includes correspondence, statements, researches and newsclippings
- Philippine News Survey, April 16-30, 1988-March 12-25, 1997, 1988-04-16-1997-03-25 (Box 37, Folder 16)
- Philippine Witness, May 1985-March 1995, 1985-05-1995-03 (Box 37, Folder 17)
- Philippine Witness, May 1985-March 1995, 1985-05-1995-03 (Box 37, Folder 18)
- "Philippine Council celebrates 25 years", 1992-05-11-1997 (Box 37, Folder 19)
- CCHRP: Urgent action alert (UA 92-1-2), 1992-05-11-1997 (Box 37, Folder 19)
- Press release by People's Task Force for Bases Clean-up, 1992-05-11-1997 (Box 37, Folder 19)
- Christianity and Crisis, May 11, 1992, 1992-05-11-1997 (Box 37, Folder 19)
- Freedom From Debt Coalition (Publications), Date unknown (Box 38)
- National Ecumenical Conference on the Philippines (NECP), Campaign Coordinating Committee (1988-1989), 1988-1989 (Box 38)
- NECP, Campaign Coordinating Committee, 1990-1991 (Box 38)
- NECP, Campaign Coordinating Committee, 1989-1990 (Box 38)
- NECP, Campaign Coordinating Committee, 1991-1992 (Box 38)
- NECP, Campaign Coordinating Committee, 1992 (Box 38)
- NECP, Campaign Coordinating Committee, 1992-1993 (Box 38)
- NECP, Philadelphia, 1986, 1986 (Box 38)
- NECP, Chicago, Conference Report 1988, 1988 (Box 38)
- NECP, Ohio, 10th Annual conference, 1994, 1994 (Box 38)
- International Ecumenical Conference on the Philippines, New York 1983, 1983 (Box 38)
- SAP (Structural Adjustment Policy), Date unknown (Box 38)
- Philippine Debt, clippings, articles, 1987-1989, 1987-1989 (Box 38)
- Philippine Bases, 1990, 1992, 1990-1992 (Box 38)
- US Bases Withdrawl, clippings, 1992-1993, 1992-1993 (Box 38)
- Piglas-Diwa, (Women and Development), Vol V, no. 3, 1992, 1992 (Box 38)
- Salinlahi Foundation, Inc. (Alliance for Children's Concerns) 1992-1993, 1992-1993 (Box 38)
- Gabriela (1983-1993), 1983-1993 (Box 38)
- Philippine Development Forum 1991, 1st Annual membership conference, Date unknown (Box 38)
- Debt Issues, Speeches by L. San Jose, M. Sta. Ana, L. Briones, E. De Dios, J. Salonga (1990), 1990 (Box 38)
- National Movement for Civil Liberties, Bulletin Boards, 1992-1993, 1992-1993 (Box 38)
- Debt, News clippings, 1990, 1990 (Box 38)
- Philippine Debt, clippings, article, 1988, 1993, 1988-1993 (Box 38)
- Alliance for Philippine Concerns, Washington, 1988-1989, 1988-1989 (Box 38)
- Various newsletters on Philippines, Date unknown (Box 38)
- Kentucky Philippine Action Committee, Date unknown (Box 38)
- Church Watch (Phil-Australia Forum, 1992), 1992 (Box 38)
- Philippine Issues, vol 6, no 5, 1992, 1992 (Box 38)
- Philippine Bulletin, 1987 (Box 38)
  Philippines Resource Center, Australia
- Philippine Update no 12, 1991-08 (Box 38)
  Phil. Solidarity Network of Aotearoa
- The Philippines Compass, 1992-1993 (Box 38)
  Committee for Philippine/American Solidarity and Support, NY
- Forum for Philippine Alternatives (Washington, DC, 1992), 1992 (Box 38)
- Friends of the Filipino People, Durham, NC (1988, 1992), 1998-1992 (Box 38)
- Philippine-American Workers International Solidarity Committee, 1994, 1994 (Box 38)
- Philippine Center for Immigrant Rights, NY, 1988, 1988 (Box 38)
- Philippine Resource Center, Berkeley, CA, 1988, 1988 (Box 38)
- Philippine Support Committee, Madison, Wisconsin, 1988, 1988 (Box 38)
- Philippine Workers Support Committee, Honolulu, 1991, 1991 (Box 38)
- Philippine Workers Support Committee, Seattle, 1994, 1994 (Box 38)
- Washington Forum on the Philippines, 1990, 1992, 1990-1992 (Box 38)
- Tanglaw, newsletter, Filipino Association for Community Education, 1988-1990, 1988-1990 (Box 38)
- Philippine Interlinks, Seattle, WA, 1990, 1990 (Box 38)
- Philippine Study Group in Minnesota, 1992, 1992 (Box 38)
- Meeting, Harrisburg, PA, 1988, 1988 (Box 38)
- Hawaii Church Committee for Human Rights in the Philippines, 1988, 1991, 1988-1991 (Box 38)
- Philippine American Ecumenical Fellowship, Raynham, MA, 1989 (Box 38)
- International Human Rights Coalition of Los Angeles, 1989, Date unknown (Box 38)
- CAUSE-Philippines (SF Bay Area), 1988, 1988 (Box 38)
- Columban Fathers Justice and Peace Office, Washington, DC, 1987, 1987 (Box 38)
- Network, (A National Social Justice Lobby) Washington DC, 1988, 1992, 1988-1992 (Box 38)
- US Catholic Conference, Washington DC, 1985, 1985 (Box 38)
- American Baptist church, PA, 1988, 1988 (Box 38)
- Church of the Brethren, Ill, 1992, 1992 (Box 38)
- Christian Church, Intl Human Rights Program, IN, 1988-1991, 1988-1991 (Box 38)
- Letter by Rt. Rev. Lyman C. Ogilby, Episcopal Church, USA, 1989, 1989 (Box 38)
- Maryknoll Mission Institute, 1986, 1992, 1986-1992 (Box 38)
- Maryknoll Sisters, Quezon City, 1987, 1987 (Box 38)
- Medical Mission Sisters, 1987, 1993, 1987-1993 (Box 38)
- Mennonite Concilation Service Newsletter, 1986-1992, 1986-1992 (Box 38)
- Unitarian Universalist Service Committee, Boston, 1989, 1989 (Box 38)
- Passionist Missions, NJ, 1983-1984, 1983-1984 (Box 38)
- Presbyterian Church, 1990, 1990 (Box 38)
- Church Network on the Philippines, 1990, 1990 (Box 38)
- Philippinwa Bases Network, Chicago, Ill, 1991, 1991 (Box 38)
- Anti-Bases, misc, 1992, 1992 (Box 38)
- League of Filipino Students-USA, Date unknown (Box 38)
- Philippine Environmental Support Network, Date unknown (Box 38)
- Philippine Study/Action Group, Kansas, Date unknown (Box 38)
- SYNAPSES, 1992, 1992 (Box 38)
- Concerned Youth for Philippines, Seattle, 1992, 1992 (Box 38)
- St. Peter's United Church of Christ, Pittsburgh, 1990, 1990 (Box 38)
- Philippine Advocacy Network, MI, 1989, 1989 (Box 38)
- Philadelphia-Philippines Working Group, Date unknown (Box 38)
- Oregon Committee for Philippine Concerns, Date unknown (Box 38)
- Ohio Coalition for Philippine Concerns, Date unknown (Box 38)
- University Christian Movement in New England, Date unknown (Box 38)
- United Church of Christ, Date unknown (Box 38)
- United Methodist Church, Date unknown (Box 38)
- Unitarian Universalist Service Committee, Date unknown (Box 38)
- 2nd Conference on Peace Disarmament and Symbiosis in the Asia-Pacific (PDSAP), April 29-May 1, 1994, 1994-04-29-1994-05-01 (Box 39)
- Human Rights Reports, 1993-1995, PAHRA, US Dept of State, Task Force Detainees Philippines, 1993-1995 (Box 39)
- Task Force Detainees Philippines Papers, 1995, 1995 (Box 39)
- Amnesty International Reports 1994, 1995, 1994-1995 (Box 39)
- Migrant Workers Clippings, 1994-1995, 1994-1995 (Box 39)
- Marcos-Class Action Suit 1994-1995, 1994-1995 (Box 39)
- Human rights articles, Date unknown (Box 39)
- Political Prisoners 1995, 1995 (Box 39)
- Church Coalition for Human Rights in the Philippines (CCHRP) 1994, 1994 (Box 39)
- CCHRP, Chris Batan, 1994, 1994 (Box 39)
- Canada-Asia Working Group, 1994, 1994 (Box 39)
- RP Commission on Human Rights, 1994, 1994 (Box 39)
- Interplanetary Human Rights Network, 1994, 1994 (Box 39)
- PAHRA and CCHRP, 1994, 1994 (Box 39)
- Promotion of Church People's Rights and PAHRA, 1994, 1994 (Box 39)
- Task Force Detainees Philippines Papers, 1994, 1994 (Box 39)
- James Rowe Murder Case, 1989, 1989 (Box 39)
- US State Dept, Human Rights Report 1993, 1993 (Box 39)
- TFDP Paper, 1994-1995, 1994-1995 (Box 39)
- Political Prisoners, clippings, 1995, 1995 (Box 39)
- Jaime Tadeo, 1992-1994, 1992-1994 (Box 39)
- James Tadeo, US Visit, June 1994, 1994-06 (Box 39)
- Santa Clara, Batangas, TFDP 1994, 1994 (Box 39)
- Mahagsay, Agusan Del Sur, 1994, 1994 (Box 39)
- Marag Valley, Kalinga, 1994, 1994 (Box 39)
- Masinloc, Zambales, 1994, 1994 (Box 39)
- Statistical summaries, 1994 (Box 39)
  Political prisoners, HR abuses
- Amnesty Program 1994, 1994 (Box 39)
- Human Rights and Environment 1994, 1994 (Box 39)
- Non-HR clippings, 1994, 1994 (Box 39)
- HR clippings, 1994, 1994 (Box 39)
- Death Sentence 1994, 1994 (Box 39)
- PAHRA split 1994, 1994 (Box 39)
- Philippine Foreign Aid, Date unknown (Box 39)
- Freedom from Debt Coalition, papers, 1994, 1994 (Box 39)
- Ecumenical Bishops' Forum (1991-1992), 1991-1992 (Box 39)
- Promotion of Church People's Rights (1990-1991), 1990-1991 (Box 39)
- Basic Christian Communities (BCC-CO) 1988, 1988 (Box 39)
- Association of Major Religious Orders (1986-1991), 1986-1991 (Box 39)
- Catholic Bishop's Conference of the Philippines (1985-1989), 1985-1989 (Box 39)
- CONTAK Philippines, 1986-1991 (Box 39)
  Church Office for International Relations and News Analysis Network
- Ecumenical Forum for Church Response 1991, 1991 (Box 39)
- Philippine Alliance of Human Rights Advocates (PAHRA) 1992, 1992 (Box 39)
- Task Force Detainees (TFD) 1990, 1992, 1990-1992 (Box 39)
- Third World Movement Against Exploitation of Women 1998, 1998 (Box 39)
- United Church of Christ in the Philippines (UCCP) 1987-1993, 1987-1993 (Box 39)
- United Methodist Church in the Philippines (UMC) 1980,1985, 1980-1985 (Box 39)
- Buklod Center (12/2), Date unknown (Box 39)
- Cordillera Women's Education and Resource Center, Inc., Date unknown (Box 39)
- Center for development Programs in the Cordillera, Inc, Date unknown (Box 39)
- Children's Rehabilitation Center, Ermita, Date unknown (Box 39)
- Citizen's Disaster Response Center (1991, 1992), 1991-1992 (Box 39)
- Kanaiyahan Foundation, Inc. (Davao City), Date unknown (Box 39)
- Medical Action Group, letters (1991), 1991 (Box 39)
- National Federation of Sugar Workers (1994), 1994 (Box 39)
- Nuclear Free Philippines (1985, 1989, 1991), 1985-1991 (Box 39)
- Conference on National Unity, Survival and Rehabilitation (1990), 1990 (Box 39)
- Philippine Global Exchange, Date unknown (Box 39)
- Church Coalition for Human Rights in the Philippines, Washington (1991), 1991 (Box 39)
- Ecumenical Partnership for International Concerns 1990, 1990 (Box 39)
- Salinlahi Foundation, Inc. 1995 (letter), 1995 (Box 39)
- Institute for Popular Democracy, Inc. 1992, 1992 (Box 39)
- Institute for Religion and Culture, Inc. (Women's Program), Date unknown (Box 39)
- Philippine International Forum (1991, 1992, 1993), 1991-1993 (Box 39)
- National Secretariat for Social Action, Date unknown (Box 39)
- National Council of Churches in the Philippines (1988, 1991), 1988-1991 (Box 39)
- National Economic Forum for Church Response (NEFCC) (1984, 1988), 1984-1988 (Box 39)
- Freedom from Debt Coalition (1987), 1987-1993 (Box 39)
- Institute of Religion and Culture, 1993, Date unknown (Box 40)
- Unlabeled folder, Date unknown (Box 40)
- Newsclippings, on Phil. religious, 1970s, 1970 (Box 40)
- Newsclippings, on Phil. religious, 1980-91, 1980-1991 (Box 40)
- Newsclippings, on Phil. religious, 1982, 1982 (Box 40)
- Newsclippings, on Phil. religious, 1983, 1983 (Box 40)
- Newsclippings, on Phil. religious, 1984, 1984 (Box 40)
- Newsclippings, on Phil. religious, 1985, 1985 (Box 40)
- Newsclippings, on Phil. religious, 1986, 1986 (Box 40)
- Newsclippings, on Phil. religious, 1987, 1987 (Box 40)
- Newsclippings, on Phil. religious, 1988, 1988 (Box 40)
- Papers by A. Lin Neumann and Rebecca Asedillo, Date unknown (Box 40)
- Freedom from Debt Coalition, papers, Date unknown (Box 40)
- Bataan Nuclear Plant Issues, Date unknown (Box 40)
- Bataan Nuclear Plant, Westinghouse (1991-1993), 1991-1993 (Box 40)
- Asian Development Bank response to letter on Masinloc Coal-Fired Power Plant, 1994, 1994 (Box 40)
- SOLJUSPAC Solar Power Projections 1993, Bishop A. Nepomuceno, 1993 (Box 40)
- Chronology of Bataan Nuclear Power Plant (BNPP), 1973-1993, 1973-1993 (Box 40)
- Bataan Nuclear Power Plant and Citibank, 1993, 1993 (Box 40)
- Bataan Nuclear Power Plant 1986, 1986 (Box 40)
- No to BNPP (Network Opposed to BNPP), 1993, 1993 (Box 40)
- BNPP, FBIS-EAS, 1992, 1992 (Box 40)
- BNPP and Union of Concerned Scientists, Washington, DC (1993), 1993 (Box 40)
- BNPP, background materials, 1992-1993, 1992-1993 (Box 40)
- Masinloc Plant and Mitsubishi, 1994, 1994 (Box 40)
- Philippine News Clippings (January-June 1994), 1994-01-1994-06 (Box 40)
- Philippine News Clippings (July-December 1994), 1994-07-1994-12 (Box 40)
- Philippine News Clippings (January-July 1995), 1995-01-1995-07 (Box 40)
- Philippine News Clippings (August-December 1995), 1995-08-1995-12 (Box 40)